Okay, you're about to do some shorter warm-up problems before we code an app.
حسنًا، كنت على وشك القيام ببعض مشاكل الإحماء الأقصر قبل أن نرمِّز تطبيقًا.
While you're working on these problems, you might want to copy over code
قد تحتاج أثناء العمل على هذه المشكلات إلى نسخ
examples into an application and actually try running it.
أمثلة الرمز في تطبيق ومحاولة تشغيله بالفعل.
Now you might be thinking about putting this sort of
والآن قد تفكر في وضع هذا النوع من
random Java code that you're testing out into your Just Java app, but
رمز جافا العشوائي الذي تختبره في تطبيق جاست جافا، ولكن
this could get a little bit messy.
قد يصبح هذا فوضويًا بعض الشيء.
So instead of potentially messing up your Just Java app,
لذلك، بدلاً من العبث في تطبيق جاست جافا،
I humbly suggest making a new app.
أقترح أن تنشئ تطبيقًا جديدًا.
Okay, so you'll want to click on the Start a new Android Studio project, and
حسنًا، ستحتاج إذًا إلى النقر على بدء مشروع أندرويد ستوديو جديد،
then you can use these specs to create your new project.
ثم يمكنك استخدام هذه المواصفات لإنشاء مشروع جديد.
If you get stuck, you can watch the solution video, or
وإذا واجهتك مشكلة، فيمكنك مشاهدة فيديو الحل، أو
I'll quickly get up and run it.
سأنهض أنا بسرعة وأقوم بتشغيله.
If you want a slower moving video, I've provided a link to the video from
وإذا كنت تريد فيديو يتحرك أبطأ، فقد وضعت رابطًا مع الفيديو من
practice set one, where you set up the happy birthday project.
مجموعة الممارسة 1، حيث يمكنك إعداد مشروع عيد الميلاد السعيد.
All right, get to it.
حسنًا، لقد فهمت.
Don't worry, I'll wait for you.
لا تقلق، سأنتظرك.